# Sadjad Asadi

+98 913 943 5192

lvlr.xaus@gmail.com github.com/lvlrSajjad

# Summary

Passionate senior software engineer with 6 years of experience managed, engineered, and developed various projects in multiple companies and also have years of open source collaboration in more than 50 projects. Seeking to learn more and expand my knowledge towards artificial intelligence and blockchain technologies to cover more areas in computer science and informatics.

### Education

Bachelor of Science
Payam-e Noor University

Feb 2016

Kerman, Iran

## Professional Experience

#### **Senior Software Engineer**

Jan 2019 - Present

#### BraveBinary LLC

- Designed, engineered, and developed a multi-purpose networking app based on Firebase, GCP, and Flutter technologies
- Engineered and developed a general-purpose backend with the ability to store and return FHIR resources via Express framework as backend & Postgres as database.
- Designed a cloud application which covers the whole billing process between services, patients, and billing providers which is under development at the moment and connected to the FHIR backend which is mentioned above.
- Designed an insurance charge estimator based on Vue.js and mySql technologies which is under development.

#### **Senior Software Engineer**

2018-2019

Magny

 Developed a location based advertising app which is based on React Native for mobile devices and AWS amplify as backend service.

Tech Lead 2018-2019

### **Esperlos**

- Led a team of eight programmers
- Designed and developed an application which connects to an electronic device and can be used as a diagnostic tool. It uses microcontrollers and a bluetooth module to transmit binary signals between the car's ECM and a mobile device.
- Designed and developed a food delivery application, in which React Native, Laravel, and mySql technologies are used.
- Developed an app for an official department which helps the IT department staff collaborate, in which React Native technologies are used.
- Designed and developed a React Native app which could track transit shippings and help the terminals to manage them.

Software Engineer 2017-2018

Owraman Intelligent Software Company

- Developed an e-Commerce social network android app
- Developed a networking library to make an offline-first app by syncing the changed data between the server and client for native Android SDK
- Designed and developed a peer-to-peer ridesharing, taxi cab, and transportation network based on React Native for mobile platforms and Yii2 Framework as backend.
- Designed and developed a car repair shop management software which has two clients for different purposes such as a mobile app for diagnosing the cars, and a web app for accounting and store management.

### **Open Source Collaborations**

#### **React Native Blur Overly**

React Native Blur Overlay Library For Ios And Android Both modules are in native Java and Objective-c languages <a href="https://github.com/lvlrSaijad/react-native-blur-overlay">https://github.com/lvlrSaijad/react-native-blur-overlay</a>

ignite-boilerplate-andross-typescript

Customized version of ignite Andross With TypeScript Support And Container Component Design pattern

https://github.com/lvlrSajjad/ignite-boilerplate-andross-typescript

#### **Ignite Studio**

A tool for easing creation and adding things to ignite projects using electron

https://github.com/lvlrSajjad/ignite-studio

#### **React Native Typescript Material UI Collection**

An accurate material ui collection designed based on material.io guidlines and made using typescript

https://github.com/lvlrSajjad/react-native-typescript-material-ui-collection

#### **Blossom**

This project following the goal of make spring framework easier to use and faster to getting start with

And a boilerplate to use with this tool

https://github.com/lvlrSajjad/java-spring-rest-mysql-boilerplate https://github.com/lvlrSajjad/blossom

#### **Ignite Andross**

Updated all dependencies and react-native version Added Container Component design pattern Changed all templates based on Container Component design pattern

https://github.com/infinitered/ignite-andross

#### Technical Skills

Software Architecture, Problem Solving, Critical Thinking, Algorithm Design, Software Engineering, Database Design, Design Patterns, Restful API, OOP, ACID, SOLID, Unit test, GCP cloud services, Aws cloud services, Android SDK, Flutter, React Native, Xcode, React, Vue, Angular, jQuery, Three.js, Laravel, Node/ Express, Electron, .Net, MySQL, Postgres, MongoDB, Firestore, Js/ Es6, Php, Java, C++, C#

# References

### Kaveh Mirzaei

### **Principal Member of Technical Staff**

AT&T Services

(347) 570-7638

km917j@att.com

### Reza Iranmanesh

Level 6

## Google

(614) 649-7213

kkduck@uiowa.edu